{"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Meow' and love to play with yarn. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I like to drink milk."},{"text":"🐈‍⬛ I have soft fur."},{"text":"🐾 I have whiskers and a tail."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I bark and wag my tail when I'm happy. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I love to chew on bones."},{"text":"🚶 I go for walks with my owner."},{"text":"🏡 I guard the house."}],"options":[{"label":"Fish","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I quack and swim in the pond. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌾 I eat weeds."},{"text":"🐥 My babies are called ducklings."},{"text":"🪶 I have feathers and webbed feet."}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I am big and gray and have a long trunk. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥜 I love peanuts."},{"text":"🐘 I have big ears."},{"text":"🌿 I live in Africa and Asia."}],"options":[{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I have a long neck and eat leaves from tall trees. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦒 I am the tallest mammal."},{"text":"spots I have brown spots all over."},{"text":"🍃 I like to eat acacia leaves"}],"options":[{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Giraffe","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I hop around and have a pouch for my baby. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🇦🇺 I come from Australia."},{"text":"🌱 I like to eat plants."},{"text":"🦘 I am a marsupial."}],"options":[{"label":"Kangaroo","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Panda","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I have black and white stripes and live in Africa. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦓 I look a bit like a horse."},{"text":"🏞️ I live on the grassy plains."},{"text":"👪 I live in groups called herds."}],"options":[{"label":"Leopard","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cheetah","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I live in the ocean and have eight arms. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌊 I am an invertebrate."},{"text":"🐙 My arms are called tentacles."},{"text":"🎨 I can change colors."}],"options":[{"label":"Starfish","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Octopus","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Seahorse","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I fly at night and catch insects. People think I'm scary, but I'm helpful. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦇 I am a mammal."},{"text":"🌃 I use echolocation to find my way."},{"text":"🍎 Some of my species eat fruit!"}],"options":[{"label":"Owl","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Butterfly","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I am a reptile with a hard shell that carries my home on my back. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐢 I am very slow."},{"text":"🥬 I like to eat lettuce."},{"text":"🏜️ Some of us live in deserts, others in the sea."}],"options":[{"label":"Snake","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Turtle","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Lizard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}}],"transport":[{"level":"1","type":"transport","question":"I have wheels and go 'vroom vroom'! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚗 I have an engine."},{"text":"👪 I can take your family places."},{"text":"🛣️ You see me on the road."}],"options":[{"label":"Car","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Banana","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Book","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"2","type":"transport","question":"I float on the water and take people places. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌊 I am big and can carry many people."},{"text":"⚓ I often travel on the ocean."},{"text":"💨 I might have sails or an engine."}],"options":[{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Boat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bicycle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"3","type":"transport","question":"I fly high in the sky and have wings. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"✈️ I can take you to faraway lands."},{"text":"☁️ You can see me above the clouds."},{"text":"⛽ I use fuel to fly."}],"options":[{"label":"Helicopter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Scooter","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"4","type":"transport","question":"I have two wheels and you pedal to make me go. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚲 You can ride me in the park."},{"text":"⛑️ It's good to wear a helmet when riding me."},{"text":"🦶 You use your feet to move me."}],"options":[{"label":"Bicycle","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Truck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Train","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"5","type":"transport","question":"I travel on tracks and carry lots of people. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🛤️ I make a 'choo choo' sound."},{"text":"🚦 I stop at stations to pick up passengers."},{"text":"🚝 Some of me go very fast!"}],"options":[{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Train","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Motorbike","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"6","type":"transport","question":"I drive on roads and stop to pick up many people. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚌 I have many seats inside."},{"text":"🛑 I often stop at bus stops."},{"text":"🗺️ I follow a route."}],"options":[{"label":"Scooter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Taxi","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"7","type":"transport","question":"I'm like a car, but I take you anywhere you want, for a price! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚕 You can call me using a phone."},{"text":"🚖 I have a meter to count the cost."},{"text":"🗺️ I know all the streets!"}],"options":[{"label":"Taxi","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Skateboard","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Firetruck","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"8","type":"transport","question":"I have a big ladder and help put out fires. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚨 I have a loud siren."},{"text":"👨‍🚒 Firefighters ride in me."},{"text":"💧 I carry water to fight fires."}],"options":[{"label":"Garbage truck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Firetruck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Ambulance","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"9","type":"transport","question":"I rescue people who are hurt and take them to the hospital quickly. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚑 I have a siren and flashing lights."},{"text":"🏥 I have doctors and nurses inside."},{"text":"🩺 I help people feel better."}],"options":[{"label":"School bus","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ambulance","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tow truck","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"10","type":"transport","question":"I am a type of transport that helps build tall buildings. I can lift heavy materials high up in the air. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🏗️ I have a long arm that can swing around."},{"text":"🚧 You can find me at construction sites."},{"text":"🔩 I am used to put things in place."}],"options":[{"label":"Crane","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Dump truck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Monster truck","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}}]}